

JESICA ROMINA SIEIRO



www.github.com/JesicaSieiro | www.jesicasieiro.wixsite.com/cosa-de-sistemas JESICA.SIEIRO@GMAIL.COM | VIAMONTE 50 | LA MATANZA | BUENOS AIRES | ARGENTINA



ABOUT ME

Hello! My name is Jesica, but everyone calls me 'Bachi'. I have worked in programming for 6 years, mainly in backend, but I consider myself a generalist programmer because I have acquired a lot of knowledge about frontend throughout these years.

I enjoy working as a team, learning as I find ways to overcome the challenges of each project. My main experience is in the development of desktop applications, but I am also interested in developing web pages and video games.

A文 LANGUAGES

SPANISH: Native language in Argentina.

ENGLISH: Basic professional competence.

ITALIAN: Intermediate level.



JOB EXPERIENCE

☐ BACKEND DEVELOPER

Federal Penitentiary Service (Nov 2013 - Oct 2019)

- Junior developer of C # and Sql Server applications.

Magiana S.A. (Ago. 2010 - Dic. 2010)

- Receptionist.
- Customer Support. Correspondence. Claims.
- File Control.

□ ADMINISTRATIVE EMPLOYEE

Dismill SRL.-Distributor (Mar. 2010 - Ago. 2010)

- Administrative Tasks. Billing.
- Customer Support. Merchandise reception.
- Cash management. Deal with Sellers and Suppliers.

ADMINISTRATIVE RECEPTIONIST

L.A. Investment Company (Mar. 2008 - Feb. 2009)

- Secretary of the Presidency, agenda management.
- Administrative receptionist, customer service. payment manager, purchase and control of library supplies and cleaning.



OTHER EXPERIENCE

- Freelance work of maintenance of social networks (Instagram and Facebook) of ACIM

Modification and maintenance of the ACIM Website (http://www.acim.org.ar/)



 \Box

 \Box

EDUCATION

GRADUATE IN TECHNOLOGY MANAGEMENT UNLaM (2019 - 2020)

> UNIVERSITY TECHNIQUE IN WEB DEVELOPMENT

UNLaM (2011 - 2018)

PRODUCT OWNER BY SCRUM INC. Scrum Inc (2021)

SCRUM MASTER BY SCRUM INC. Scrum Inc (2021)



♦ KEY SKILLS

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES & FRAMEWORKS

- C#
- ASP.NET.
- JAVA SCRIP
- HTML
- CSS
- PYTHON.
- JAVA.
- OOP (Object Oriented Programming)
- SQL
- Entity Framework
- Bootstrap
- SQL Management Studio
- MySQL
- GIT
- Wordpress